{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Synthetic Grass Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/46329/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46329,"taskName":"Landscape - Install Synthetic Grass for Putting Greens, Play Areas, etc.","taskDescription":"Install Synthetic Grass for Landscaping, Putting Greens, Play Areas, etc.","xmTaskDescriptor":"Synthetic Grass Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":253,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Landscape Synthetic Grass Putting Play","textMessagingName":"Synthetic Grass","rolloverLongDesc":"Synthetic turf, alternative to real grass - designed to be realistic \u0026 maintenance-free.","rolloverShortDesc":"Alternative to real grass - designed to be realistic \u0026 maintenance-free.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Synthetic Grass for Landscaping, Putting Greens, Play Areas, etc..  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Artificial Grass \u0026 Turf Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Synthetic Grass Install","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":47,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Synthetic Grass for Play Area Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Landscape - Install Synthetic Grass for Landscaping, Putting Greens, Play Areas, etc.","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Landscape Project","urlName":"Install-Synthetic-Grass-Artificial-Turf-for-Putting-Greens-and-Landscaping","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Artificial Grass \u0026 Turf Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews for Synthetic Grass","searchKeywords":"Landscape,Synthetic,Grass,Putting,Play,artificial,astro,back,architect,landsacping,geo-landscaping,front,landscaper,fake,backyard,yard,pool,grasses,ornamental,lawn,,,landscapers,astroturf,turf,Greens,Landscaping","emcCategoryOid":-12046,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1014,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46329/":{"taskOID":46329,"originalTaskOID":46329,"setID":1014,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":200137,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Synthetic Grass","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of synthetic grass would you like to install?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17222,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Landscape grass","answerDisplayText":"Landscape grass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17223,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Athletic turf","answerDisplayText":"Athletic turf","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17224,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Golf - backyard putting green","answerDisplayText":"Golf - backyard putting green","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17225,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Golf - indoor putting green","answerDisplayText":"Golf - indoor putting green","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17226,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Playground grass","answerDisplayText":"Playground grass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17227,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bocci ball turf","answerDisplayText":"Bocci ball turf","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17228,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dog run turf","answerDisplayText":"Dog run turf","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7187,"questionDisplayText":"Approx. Size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate size of the area you would like to install the synthetic grass?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11227,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11228,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11229,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11230,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":200137,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Synthetic Grass","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of synthetic grass would you like to install?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17222,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Landscape grass","answerDisplayText":"Landscape grass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17223,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Athletic turf","answerDisplayText":"Athletic turf","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17224,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Golf - backyard putting green","answerDisplayText":"Golf - backyard putting green","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17225,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Golf - indoor putting green","answerDisplayText":"Golf - indoor putting green","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17226,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Playground grass","answerDisplayText":"Playground grass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17227,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bocci ball turf","answerDisplayText":"Bocci ball turf","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17228,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dog run turf","answerDisplayText":"Dog run turf","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17222,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Landscape grass","answerDisplayText":"Landscape grass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17223,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Athletic turf","answerDisplayText":"Athletic turf","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17224,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Golf - backyard putting green","answerDisplayText":"Golf - backyard putting green","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17225,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Golf - indoor putting green","answerDisplayText":"Golf - indoor putting green","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17226,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Playground grass","answerDisplayText":"Playground grass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17227,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bocci ball turf","answerDisplayText":"Bocci ball turf","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17228,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dog run turf","answerDisplayText":"Dog run turf","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7187,"questionDisplayText":"Approx. Size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate size of the area you would like to install the synthetic grass?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11227,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11228,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11229,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11230,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11227,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11228,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11229,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11230,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}